https://www.nclrights.org/privacy-policy/

Ayuda
Privacy Policy
The National Center for Lesbian Rights has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our web site, as well as how we handle and secure the privacy of our donors’ personal information.
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the web site located at the URL https://www.nclrights.org/
In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use. The National Center for Lesbian Rights reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of:1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the site;2. Who collects such information;3. How such information is used;4. With whom your information may be shared;5. What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;6. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and,7.How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to The National Center for Lesbian Rights by sending an email to development@nclrights.org. Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information:Our registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, format preference (HTML vs. Text), address, interests, and similar information. We do not request or store sensitive information from our visitors, such as credit card or social security numbers. At any point and time you can opt-out of receiving communications from us by logging into our website and selecting the ‘manage your profile’ link in the top-right hand corner of the page OR you can notify us by calling 415-392-6257 or email us at development@nclrights.org.
Internet Protocol Address:We collect an IP address from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server,administer our site, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Use of “Cookies”:Our site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our site. Cookies are pieces of information that some web sites transfer to the computer that is browsing that web site and are used for record-keeping purposes at many web sites. Use of cookies makes web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular web site and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.
Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them.
Security:All information provided to The National Center for Lesbian Rights is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of The National Center for Lesbian Rights. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
How We Protect Your Information:The National Center for Lesbian Rights is extremely protective of the information gathered through its fundraising endeavors and website. Our website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. Our web server is located in a locked, secure environment. When you contribute to the National Center for Lesbian Rights online, we use a secure server and encryption to protect your financial and other personal information during transmission.
The National Center for Lesbian Rights follows the Association of Fundraising Professionals’ Ethical Guidelines to the Code of Ethical Principles and Standards of Professional Practice. Occasionally, the National Center for Lesbian Rights does exchange or rent lists with like-minded organizations through bonded third-party vendors. These organizations are never given information about our membership directly. We carefully screen each mailing before we allow it to be sent to our membership. Information pertaining to the National Center for Lesbian Rights’ board members, Anniversary Circle members, Anniversary Celebration sponsors, and/or $100+ donors is never—under any circumstance—released to external entities for the purpose of list exchanges or rentals. Other than name and postal mailing address, none of the other information provided via our website (including email address) is ever shared with other organizations or parties.
The National Center for Lesbian Rights does not specifically ask children under 18 for any information and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from or about them.
How to Opt-out or Unsubscribe From Mailing Lists:Those wishing to opt-out of receiving communications from the National Center for Lesbian Rights (“do not contact”), or from being included in list exchanges with like-minded organizations (“do not exchange”) can simply contact our development department at development@nclrights.org or via phone at 415.392.6257, or via US mail at 870 Market St., Suite 370, San Francisco, CA 94102.
How to Correct Information You Have Provided:You may correct and/or change any information regarding your membership by contacting our development department at development@nclrights.org or via phone at 415.392.6257.
Tell-A-Friend:If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. The National Center for Lesbian Rights will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. The National Center for Lesbian Rights stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.
Other Web Sites:Our site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another web site for which The National Center for Lesbian Rights has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.
How to Contact Us:If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at:The National Center for Lesbian Rights870 Market Street, Suite 370San Francisco, CA 94102415.392.6257
development@nclrights.org
Recent Posts
Uplifting Transgender Voices – Our Client’s Story
From the Desk of Imani Rupert-Gordon – October 2020
Latinx Heritage Month
NCLR’s Response to Justices Alito and Thomas
From the Desk of Imani Rupert-Gordon – September 2020
TopicsAdditional Civil Rights
Gmail
HomepageAbout UsMission & HistoryWho We AreOur Voices blogPress & MediaFinancials & ReportsJobs & OpportunitiesOur WorkBorn PerfectDiscriminationEducationEldersEmploymentFaith & ReligionHealthcareHousing & Public AccommodationsSportsRacial & Economic JusticeCriminalization & IncarcerationLegal Aid & Legal ServicesRace & PovertyRural CommunitiesYouthEducationFoster CareJuvenile JusticeTransgender YouthRelationships & FamilyMarriage & RelationshipsParentingReproductive JusticeImmigration & AsylumCases & AdvocacyLegislation & PolicyGet InvolvedDonate NowOther Ways to GiveOther Ways to Support Our WorkEventsGet HelpObtenga AyudaResources and PublicationsObtenga AyudaContact UsDonate
